chalyaara.com 2019-06-13

# Chalyaara

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which “ChalYaara Travel Solutions LLP“ collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User“) of the www.chalyaara.com website (“Site“). This privacy policy applies to the site and all products and services offered by us. 

**DISCLAIMER**

The material displayed on this website, from time to time, (the “Material”) is provided “as is“ without warranties or conditions of any kind either expressed or implied. To the fullest extent possible under applicable law, www.chalyaara.com disclaims all warranties and conditions respecting the Material, expressed or implied, including but not limited to, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or other violation of rights. “ChalYaara Travel Solutions LLP“ does not warrant or make any other representations regarding the use, accuracy, timelines, applicability, performance, security, availability or reliability of this website or any sites linked to this site, or the results from the use of this website or any sites linked to this website, or otherwise respecting the materials on this website or any sites linked to this website.

All information on this website, www.chalyaara.com is subject to change without notice. “ChalYaara Travel Solutions LLP“ does not endorse any of the organizations referred to on this website. Any links to other websites are provided for convenience only; “ChalYaara Travel Solutions LLP“ does not review or monitor the content of those sites and disclaims any responsibility for their content and accuracy. “ChalYaara Travel Solutions LLP“ does not make any representations or warranties as to the reliability, financial condition or suitability for any particular purpose of any organization referred to on this website. You are advised to make your own inquiries of any organization presented on this site to determine if they are satisfactory for your purposes. “ChalYaara Travel Solutions LLP“ disclaims any liability in negligence or otherwise for any loss or damage which may occur as a result of reliance on any of this material

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, social security number. Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identifying information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities. 

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identifiable information about users whenever they interact with our site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about the user's means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilized, and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies“ to enhance user experience. The user's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

We may collect and utilize users personal information for the following points.

  * To improve customer service

The information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently

  * To personalize the user experience

We may use information in the aggregate, to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

  * To improve our Site

We may use the feedback you provide to improve our products and services.service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

  *   * To personalize the user experience

We may use the feedback you provide to improve our products and services.service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

  *   * To process payments

We may use the information users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide

  *   * To share your information with third parties

We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.

  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature

To send users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

  *   * To send periodic emails

We may use the email address to send user information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, or other requests. If user decides to choose our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the user would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or user may contact us via our Site. How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.

Private and sensitive data exchange between the site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected by digital signatures. Our site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for users.

**Sharing your personal information**

We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our site that provide link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites, which have a link to our site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

The ads appearing on our site may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identifying information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information“ and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

**Compliance with children online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

We have the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. The posting of changes to this private policy will consider your acceptance.

Contacting us Registered Office

### ChalYaara Travel Solutions LLP

G-129, 2nd Floor, Sector-63,  
Noida, Uttar Pradesh  
INDIA - 201301  
Phone No : 8803838803  
Email ID : info@chalyaara.com
